https://www.skiesunlimited.com/terms-and-conditions.html

I'm a new customer
Registering a new account is quick and easy...
Categories
Telescopes Eyepieces Telescope Accessories Mounts Imaging Accessories Used and Demo Brands More
Celestron Telescopes
Celestron NexStar SE 9 Celestron Advanced VX 9 Celestron NexStar Evolution 6 Celestron CGEM II 8 Celestron CGX 9 Celestron CGX-L 7 Celestron StarSense Explorer 2 Celestron SkyProdigy 1 Celestron NexStar SLT 4 Celestron Omni XLT 3 Celestron Optical Tube Assemblies 8 Celestron CPC 3 Celestron CPC Deluxe 3 Celestron Rowe-Ackerman Schmidt Astrograph 8 Celestron AstroMaster 7 Celestron FirstScope 2
Celestron Telescope Mounts 5
Celestron Eyepieces and Barlows
Celestron Omni 7 Celestron X-Cel LX 7 Celestron Barlows 3 Celestron Eyepiece and Filter Sets 2 Celestron Ultima Duo
Celestron Telescope Accessories
Celestron Counterweights 4 Celestron Diagonals and Adapters 6 Celestron Electronic Accessories 12 Celestron Filters 7 Celestron Finders 4 Celestron Power Accessories 8 Celestron Miscellaneous Accessories 8
Celestron Imaging Accessories 26
Celestron Binoculars
Celestron SkyMaster 5 Celestron SkyMaster Pro 2 Celestron Nature DX 3 Celestron Trailseeker Binoculars 4 Celestron Granite ED 2
Celestron Spotting Scopes
Celestron Ultima 3 Celestron Trailseeker 3 Celestron Regal M2 ED 3
Celestron Microscopes 12
Coronado 9
DayStar Filters 16
Explore Scientific
Explore Scientific Telescopes
AR Doublet Series 3 ED APO FCD1 Series 3 ED APO FCD100 Triplet Series 5 ED APO FPL-53 Series 2
Explore Scientific Eyepieces
Explore Scientific 82 Degree Eyepieces 11 Explore Scientific 92 Degree LE Series Eyepieces 2 Explore Scientific 100 Degree Eyepieces 6
Explore Scientific Telescope Mounts 4
Explore Scientific Telescope Accessories 6
Howie Glatter 13
iOptron
iOptron Center Balance Mounts 8
iOptron Telescope Mounts 3
iOptron Camera Mounts 3
iOptron Accessories 12
Meade Telescopes
Meade Beginner Telescopes 3 Meade LX65 4 Meade LX85 7 Meade LightBridge Plus 3 Meade LX90 3 Meade LX200 4 Meade LX600 3 Meade LX850 3 Meade LightSwitch 2
Meade Telescope Mounts 3
Meade Telescope Mount Accessories 2
Meade Eyepieces and Barlows
Meade Series 5000 HD-60 Meade Ultra Wide Angle 4
Meade Telescope Accessories 12
Meade Imaging Accessories 5
Pacific Design 6
Revolution Imager 9
Rigel Systems 5
Sirius Technologies 7
Skies Unlimited 1
Sky and Telescope
Sky-Watcher
Sky-Watcher Telescopes
Sky-Watcher EvoStar ED Doublets 6 Sky-Watcher Esprit Apochromatic Triplets 4 Sky-Watcher Classic Dobsonians 3 Sky-Watcher Flextube Dobsonians 3 Sky-Watcher Flextube SynScan Dobsonians 5 Sky-Watcher Quattro Imaging Newtonians 3
Sky-Watcher Mounts 11
Sky-Watcher Mount Accessories 9
Sky-Watcher Imaging Accessories 5
Spectrum Telescope 27
Starizona 6
Starlight Instruments
Feather Touch Focusers 7
Focuser Adapters 29
Takahashi Telescopes
Takahashi Refractors 6 Takahashi Mewlon 3 Takahshi Astrographs 2
Takahashi Tube Holders 10
Takahashi Telescope Accessories 4
Takahashi Imaging Accessories 14
Takahashi Telescope Mounts
Takahashi Counterweights 6
Takahashi Finders
Takahashi CCD Adapters
Telegizmos
Telegizmos Standard Dobsonian Covers 10
Telegizmos Standard Fork Mount SCT Covers 8
Telegizmos Standard Covers for Equatorial Mounted Telescopes 10
Telegizmos 365 Series Dobsonian Covers 5
Telegizmos 365 Series Fork Mount SCT Covers 6
Telegizmos 365 Series Covers for Equatorial Mounted Telescopes 6
Telegizmos Tripod Covers 2
TeleVue
TeleVue Telescopes 8
TeleVue Eyepieces
TeleVue DeLite 9 TeleVue Delos 8 TeleVue Ethos 8 TeleVue Nagler 9 TeleVue Panoptic 5 TeleVue Plossl 8 TeleVue Zoom 1
TeleVue Eyepiece Accessories 24
TeleVue Telescope Accessories
TeleVue Diagonals 6 Telescope Accessory Packages 6 TeleVue Finders 10 TeleVue Mounting Adapters 4 TeleVue Mounting Rings 4 TeleVue Filters 4
TeleVue Telescope Mounts 5
TeleVue Barlows and Powermates 10
TeleVue Imaging Accessories 32
Telrad 6
Thousand Oaks Optical
Thousand Oaks Full Aperture Solar Filters
Thousand Oaks Dew Heaters 6
Universal Astronomics
Updated February 5, 2020
Secure Ordering You may order with confidence at Skies Unlimited. Any personal information submitted via our website, including name, and address and credit card number is encrypted via SSL (Secure Socket Layer). SSL encryption is the industry standard used for secure commerce transactions over the web, preventing your personal information from being read as it travels across Internet.
We do not share your personal information with third parties. Payment Options Skies Unlimited accepts the following major credit cards for online orders: Discover, Visa, Mastercard, and American Express.
We use PayPal as our online payment processor.
We also accept payments directly from Paypal accounts.
Charges will occur immediately upon checkout. In the event of a back ordered item that cannot be shipped within a reasonable period of time, we will reverse the charge and recapture the funds on the actual date of shipment. Arrangements for other payment methods, including money orders and checks, may be made in advance by calling us at 610-327-3500. Skies Unlimited also accepts corporate and institutional purchase orders.
Sales Tax Skies Unlimited is based in the state of Pennsylvania. Orders shipped to an address within the state of Pennsylvania are subject to a 6% sales tax.
We do not charge sales tax to organizations with tax exempt status, including schools, universities, or other non-profit entities.
Some large and expensive items are drop shipped directly from the manufacturer, and may be
subject to a local sales tax if the origin and destination are within the same state. In such cases you will be contacted prior to the actual processing of your order and given the option to pay the tax or cancel the order. Shipping Policy Skies Unlimited ships via United Parcel Service (UPS) or UPS SurePost.
You will see the actual charges for all available shipping service options before committing your order. In the event of a multiple item order, the shipping charge you see may err on the high side.
When this happens we refund the difference back to the original source of funds (credit card or PayPal.) Free shipping offers apply only to the lower 48 States. International Orders Skies Unlimited does not accept international orders, and our website will not accept international addresses. In many cases our suppliers do not permit us to ship their products outside of the US. These suppliers generally will not honor the warranty on a product shipped by a US dealer to a foreign address.
Returns Returned items must be in new, unopened condition. Most such returns will be refunded 100%, minus shipping charges. We reserve the right to recover our credit card transaction costs (up to 3.5%) on any refund valued over $1000. Any items returned after having been opened, whether used or not, must be resold as used merchandise. Any such returns are subject to a restocking fee of 15% or whatever our cost to bring the merchandise back into a salable condition, whichever is greater. Note that any item we advertise as "new" is precisely that. Returned items are sold at markdown on our used page. No returns will be accepted without prior authorization and none will be accepted more than 30 days after receipt of the merchandise. All returns must be accompanied by an authorization number, which may be obtained by calling us at (610) 327-3500. Manufacturers defects are normally covered by the terms of the manufacturers? warranties, but we suggest that you contact us first for expedited service.
Printable Version
My Account
Login Register Forgot Password?
Categories
Manufacturers
Select... ADM Accessories Astrozap Atik Baader Planetarium
Bob's Knobs Celestron Coronado DayStar Filters Explore Scientific Howie Glatter Other Manufacturers...
More...
TeleVue Extension Tube 3.5"
Always a pleasure dealing with the experts at Skies Unlimited.
Eric L.
Terms & Conditions Privacy Statement Telescope Buying Advice Skies Unlimited Location And Store Hours About Us Contact Us
Terms & Conditions Privacy statement Telescope Buying Advice Skies Unlimited Location and Store Hours About Us
Links
Astonomical Society of Harrisburg Bucks-Mont Astronomical Association Chesmont Astronomical Society Chester County Astronomical Society
Special
New Arrivals On sale Manufacturers
Sitemap
Contact Us
